Miller, N mss. II, 1928-1991 LMC 2609
Lilly Library
- V. OTHER WRITINGS
  - Living Language textbook
    - Book 12, Ch. 20 (Box 14)
    - Final draft - Book 12, Ch. 4 (Box 14)
    - Final draft - Book 12, Ch. 6 (Box 14)
    - Final draft - Book 12, Ch. 8 (Box 14)
    - Final draft - Book 12, Ch. 9 (Box 14)
    - Grade 7 Outline (Box 14)
    - Grade 8 Outline (Box 14)
    - Grade 9 Outline + Ch. 3, 6 (Box 14)
    - Grade 10 + 11 Outlines (Box 14)
    - Grade 11 Ch. 1 (Box 14)
    - Grade 12 Outline (Box 14)
    - Grade 12 Ch. 1 (Box 14)
    - Grade 12 Ch. 2 (Box 14)
    - Grade 12 Ch. 5 (Box 14)
    - Grade 12 Ch. 8 (Box 14)
    - Ch. 7 Ver. 2 (Box 14)
    - Ch. 8 Ver. 2 (Box 14)
    - Ch. 9 Ver. 2 (Box 14)
    - "The Source Theme" (Box 15)
    - "A Guide to Better English" (Box 15)
    - "A Guide to Better English" Ver. 2 (Box 15)
    - "Help Yourself to Better English" (Box 15)
    - "Writing with a Purpose" (Box 15)
    - "Roads to Learning" (Box 15)
    - "Oral Presentations" (Box 15)
    - Misc 1 (Box 15)
    - Misc 2 (Box 15)
    - Misc 3 (Box 15)
  - "About short stories" (Box 15)
  - "All Souls" - One act play (Box 15)
  - "Beginnings" - 1 hour TV play Part 1 (Box 15)
  - "Beginnings" - 1 hour TV play Part 2 (Box 15)
  - "History of the Writer's Forum" (Box 15)
  - "An Insider's Guide to Getting Published" (Box 15)
  - "A Message to the Rejected" (Box 15)
  - "Spring 1944" (Box 15)
  - "The Stigmata" (Box 15)
  - Undergrad essays (Box 15)
  - Various poems - Part 1 (Box 15)
  - Various poems - Part 2 (Box 15)
  - "Wedding Night" - One act play (Box 15)
  - "What is a Winter" (Box 15)
  - "The World of the Writer" (Box 15)
  - "Writer to Reader: The Experience of Fiction" (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
- VI. JOURNALS
  - July 22-Oct 29, 1942 (Box 15)
  - Nov 5, 1942-July 5, 1943 (Box 15)
  - July 8, 1943-July 24, 1944 (Box 15)
  - Aug 6, 1944-May 2, 1945 (Box 15)
  - May 4, 1945-Jan 1, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Jan 2-Dec 31, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Jan 6, 1947-Mar 21, 1948 (Box 15)
  - Mar 24, 1948-Aug 31, 1949 (Box 15)
  - 1958-1963 (Box 15)
- VII. CORRESPONDENCE
  - 1944-1949 (Box 15)
  - 1950-1955 (Box 15)
  - 1956-1960 (Box 15)
  - 1961 Part 1 (Box 15)
  - 1961 Part 2 (Box 15)
  - 1962-1964 (Box 15)
  - 1965 Part 1 (Box 15)
  - 1965 Part 2 (Box 15)
  - 1966 (Box 15)
  - 1967 (Box 15)
  - 1968-1978 (Box 15)
  - 1980-1989 (Box 15)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - N.D. (Box 15)
  - Letters from agents (Box 15)
  - About Living Language (Box 15)
  - The Writer (Box 15)
  - Julie Hecht (Box 15)
  - Misc (Box 15)
- VIII. TEACHING MATERIALS
  - "The Fiction of Fiction" (Box 15)
  - "The Reality of Reality" I (Box 15)
  - "The Reality of Reality" II (Box 15)
  - "The Reality of Fiction" (Box 15)
  - "The Fiction of Language" I (Box 15)
  - "The Fiction of Language" II (Box 15)
  - "The Fiction of Language" III (Box 15)
  - Workshop 6 (Box 15)
  - Workshop 9 (Box 15)
  - Workshop transcript (Box 15)
  - Workshop transcript 2 (Box 15)
  - Workshop lecture (Box 15)
  - Copies of stories (Box 15)
  - Student poetry (Box 15)
  - Evaluations (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous 1 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous 2 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous 3 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous 4 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous 5 (Box 15)
- IX. MISCELLANEOUS
  - Photos (Box 15)
  - Antioch admin materials (Box 15)
  - "Combat" - William F. Vocke (Box 15)
  - "Various poems" - Lance G. Binkley (Box 15)
  - Naked in December - William Dale Smith Part 1 (Box 15)
  - Naked in December - William Dale Smith Part 2 (Box 15)
  - Naked in December - William Dale Smith Part 3 (Box 15)
  - Naked in December - William Dale Smith Part 4 (Box 15)
  - Naked in December - William Dale Smith Part 5 (Box 15)
  - Naked in December - William Dale Smith Part 6 (Box 15)
  - Newspaper clippings - Part 1 (Box 15)
  - Newspaper clippings - Part 2 (Box 15)
  - Notes on scrap paper - Part 1 (Box 15)
  - Notes on scrap paper - Part 2 (Box 15)
  - Black planner (Box 15)
  - Writing pamphlets and handbooks (Box 15)
  - Red composition notebook (Box 15)
  - Diary - bound in black (Box 15)
  - The Book of Nolan Miller -- bound in red (Box 15)
  - Periodicals
    - Various (Box 15)
    - The Philadelphia Inquirer, Dec 26, 1948 (Box 17)
    - The Writer, Jan 1947 (Box 17)
    - The Atlantic, June 1944 (Box 17)
    - Junior Bazaar, May 1947 (Box 17)
    - Today;'s Woman, Sept 1947 (Box 17)
    - Household, Nov 1945 (Box 17)
    - The Saturday Evening Post, Nov, 10 1945 (Box 17)
    - Collier's, June 9, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Collier's, Aug 18, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Collier's, Sept 8, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Collier's, Oct 27, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Collier's, June 15, 1946 (Box 17)
    - McCall's, May 1946 (Box 17)
    - Woman's Home Companion, Feb 1947 (Box 17)